(I'm Doing Great on My Own)
(A radio show is in full swing in the booth.)
Peanut butter cream bun.
- It's "Hope Song at Noon." - Yes, it is.
"Hope Song at Noon."
She's been hosting it...
- for 15 years. - Right.
- At noon. - For 15 years?
I spent my 30s, hosting this show.
Yes.
This is your DJ, Kim Shin Young, from "Hope Song at Noon."
And DJ Choi Yoo Jung.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Good work today. - You should go.
- See you next week. - Sure.
I'll make you a great dessert next time.
Sounds good.
- Good work. - Good work.
- Great job. - Good work.
- Great job today. - See you tomorrow morning.
- See you tomorrow. - Bye.
Bye, I'm off.
Do you win the Golden Mouth Award when you host a show for 10 years?
- Twenty years. - Twenty years?
I already won the Bronze Mouth Award after my tenth year.
I was the youngest winner of the Bronze Mouth Award then.
It was the first show hosted by a solo female DJ to win the award.
- It was the first show ever. - That's crazy.
If nothing...
- If you keep working... Yes. - crazy happens until 2029,
- then... - It's as long as you don't quit.
Right. As long as I don't quit, I'll win the Golden Mouth Award.
- That's impressive. - That's crazy.
Hosting a radio show for two years and a half was really tough.
- I could never go on my vacation. - Right.
- Vacation. - That's really tough.
- I mean, you could. - As for me,
hosting it for a special DJ for a week was tough.
That was tough for you?
- Why bother living then? - Seriously.
The radio show becomes part of my life.
- Like a permanent job. - Right.
(The worker with a permanent job quickly gets off work.)
You're getting off work right on time again.
(Coughing)
- Wait, you must be sick. - I've been sick lately.
It started with a pollen allergy...
- and rhinitis. - Right.
It turned out I had a throat infection.
- Throat infections are so painful. - It really was.
- Especially for DJs who must talk. - Yes.
- That's the worst. - My condition was the worst then.
- It's really painful. - It was the worst that day.
- Ji Hyeon, you also had it... - But you still went to work.
- when you had your concert. - Yes.
- You could barely talk then. - I thought it'd be the end of me.
- It really hurt. - Right.
- Throat infections last quite long. - Right.
- They last at least a month. - Yes.
Hello. Have a good day.
(Coughing)
My goodness.
Okay.
All right.
(Because of the throat infection, driving herself home is tough too.)
That's all
- Do you drive yourself around? - Yes.
I see.
Clap!
I go to the radio show on my own.
I've been working in this industry for 24 years.
But I have no idea how things work at the TV stations.
Starting with the locations,
I don't know where the waiting rooms are...
or how to get to the studios.
- "RS2." "RS3." - That was the biggest reason.
- Sometimes, we confuse the floors. - I worked in this industry...
- Right. - But we come here all the time.
It made me wonder...
if I could proudly say that...
I had been in this industry for 24 years.
So I had been on my own without an agency for a year and a half.
Then I have gotten used to doing things on my own.
One, two, three, ho
(She's gotten used to getting off work alone now.)
My house! My world.
That's part of my routine too. When I'm home, I say,
- "My house. My world." - "My house. My world."
My house is my world indeed.
(She arrives in her world by keeping up with her routine.)
(She enters the house while carrying the shoes inside.)
Wait. Why are you bringing in your shoes?
She has to put them back on the rack.
- Back in the case? - Yes.
That's the thing. My babies ought to go back inside their home too.
(The shoes go back into their home too.)
Rest up.
(She comes out to the living room after putting her shoes away.)
Okay.
Doesn't the table kind of look like a scale?
- What? - My gosh.
- Oh, this? - Come on.
Come on. Don't be like that.
(She puts the hat in the steam closet.)
Let me do that first.
- Okay. I should wash up now. - I put my hats in a steam closet.
- You have to. - Same here.
- I put hats and belts in there too. - Yes.
- People say... - Right.
It could ruin the belts, but I do it anyway...
- when I come home. - You must put everything in there.
Okay.
(Opening up)
I must put the clothes I wore...
- in the steam closet right away. - Right.
That makes things convenient. Otherwise, they get wrinkles...
- or smell. - Right.
(Striding)
(She turns on the bright bathroom lights.)
(Reaching down)
All right.
(Tossing them out)
Her house is always clean.
I installed wallpaper sheets in the bathroom.
- Oh, my. - I decorated it myself.
(The bathroom floor is meant to be kept dry.)
But humidity must be really bad for the bathroom.
- It's hard to keep it dry. - That's why...
I always have to wipe the moisture.
- Look how clean her drain is. - It's crazy...
how the silicone still looks that white.
(White silicone caulk)
- Right. - Look how white it is.
- It's white. - Yes.
What? Is that a new toilet?
(She maintains her bathroom in pristine condition.)
(She takes something out with a rustling sound.)
- What is that? - What is it?
(Spreading it out)
It pops up.
- Is that a tent? - What is it?
- Is that a hat? - What is it?
(Let me see.)
Are you going to dye your hair?
(She takes a mysterious bag next.)
Let me do this first and then wash up.
(Tying her hair)
(She ties up her hair in perfect pigtails.)
(Grabbing)
(She puts it right over her head.)
I know. Parents use that when they wash their kids' hair.
- Right. But that's the adult size. - Really?
- That's the adult size? - Yes.
It looks like a dog cone they wear after being neutered.
- What? - To prevent the hair from falling.
- Like the neck collar? - Hold on.
- I mean... - What's the point...
of my getting neutered now?
(Apologetic)
It's better to do it early...
- if you plan to get it. - Of course.
- Why do I want to give her treats? - It's not like...
- Like cat treats? - I have a long tongue.
- I don't want any treats from you. - Okay.
- I'm sorry. - They're fishy.
They're fishy.
(My Ae Ong loves them.)
(She puts on the haircut cape, the kind meant for humans.)
(Then she takes something out from a resealable bag.)
- What? - A hair clipper?
Yes.
It's good.
(She nonchalantly turns it on.)
(She starts trimming her hair then.)
Gosh, it's so messy.
(Trimming her hair skillfully)
- Gosh, she doesn't even hesitate. - That can't be easy.
Do you cut your own hair?
- I didn't know she did. - Yes.
Even I can't handle hair clippers.
- He uses scissors. - Really? Scissors?
I've cut my hair with scissors for a long time.
With kitchen scissors.
(HairClipper83 surpasses...)
(Scissors84.)
I've been cutting my own hair for ten years now.
If you look at my hair, you'll see that my hair is thick.
If I grow out the back of my hair,
it will puff up like the character in "The Smoggies."
- Like that. - I see.
At first, I diligently went...
to a hair salon in Gangnam from Mapo.
But I couldn't keep up.
- It's a hassle. - It was such a hassle.
- It's inefficient too. - Yes.
- A round trip would be two hours. - That's a lot of work.
So I decided to learn the skill.
At first, I cut my hair with a dog grooming clipper.
But I ended up shaving too much of my hair.
The back of my head looked bald like a groomed Maltese.
- That's how my hair looked. - A lot of hair gets shaved...
like that with a dog grooming clipper.
- It shaved all of my hair. - Right.
I thought if I kept using the clipper,
my skin would get irritated.
So I started to try out...
several proper hair clippers.
I can't look at the back of my head.
So I feel my hair with my fingers.
- That's how I cut it. - I didn't know you could do that.
If my hair looks too crooked, I can stop by a hair salon...
and get it trimmed again when I go out for work.
(She stops by a hair salon for a trim.)
(Whirring)
Gosh, hair clippers are hard to handle.
You stop it with your fingers.
- So the clipper doesn't go higher. - Right.
Wait. How come my face isn't showing?
I'm sorry, but my belly looks really bulging in this shot.
- That's all we can see. - Wait.
(I'm sorry, but my belly looks really bulging in this shot.)
(As she shaves the back of her head without hesitation, )
(her hair at the back of her head slowly disappears.)
- Oh, my. - She looks like she's enlisting.
(Like a recruit who has left home to enlist, )
(she mercilessly shaves the back of her head.)
(A clear line-up)
(Did I do a good job?)
(Checking herself in the mirror)
It looks good.
- Gosh. - It feels nice.
You shaved quite a lot of hair.
- It's a 2 block haircut. - I used a 3mm clipper guard.
How frequently do you cut your hair?
My hair at the back of my head grows so fast.
It grows so fast.
- Right. - I cut it once every three weeks.
I just use a 3mm clipper guard.
- You can see the back of my head. - Right.
If this part looks messy,
I could look unkempt overall.
- You look neat and nice. - I want to look neat.
You don't have to go to the hair salon.
(She takes good care of the hair at the back of her head.)
(She's done with her haircut.)
(Careful)
(Removing her head)
- That's convenient. - Yes.
- It's really convenient. - Right.
- Not to make a mess. - Then...
- you can just throw that out. - Right.
I just have to throw that out.
- That's useful. - Yes.
(Shaking)
(After giving it a good shake)
After shaking it off, I can put it back in the bag.
(She puts it back in the bag and stores it.)
(Cleaning up the hair neatly afterward)
(She removes any stray hair while taking a shower.)
All right. First...
(After a refreshing shower, )
(she starts her skincare routine.)
That's the toner.
- Yes, it's foam toner. - Right.
- It's foam toner. - It's more convenient.
I thought it was shaving foam.
No. It's not!
- Shaving foam? - Well,
- it looked like the one I use. - Why would I spray it here then?
- Some people have hair there. - Come on.
- She's not a soldier or anything. - It's...
It was the same consistency...
- of my shaving cream. - Right.
- That's toner. - So... Yes, it's toner.
- It's new. Yes. - You just apply it to your face.
You can easily spread it on your face. It's more convenient.
(She lets the toner sink in.)
Good.
Next.
(She grabs the serum next to the toner right away.)
I tried to find good products for dry and extremely dry skin.
And that's how I found that.
(She finishes up with the soothing cream.)
(Slapping hard)
(She puts them back right away.)
Oh, that.
My goodness.
(She grabs something and goes back to the basin.)
All right.
(She pours it on her foot.)
- What's that? - My foot...
- What's that? - What? Whose foot is that?
- That's my foot. - Did you seriously ask that?
Hey.
- What was that about? - She lives alone.
- I thought it was someone else. - That has to be my foot.
I thought she was washing someone else's foot.
I live alone.
- She's very flexible. - You're scaring me.
She's very flexible.
(She's washing her foot...)
(while showing off her flexibility.)
My feet have been getting super sweaty lately.
So I have a product I use for my sweaty feet.
It cools down my feet and stops them from getting sweaty.
I always stock up on this product.
I always make sure I have spares.
She's sharing a lot of useful tips.
(An essential item she always keeps in stock)
(She's finally done with her full-body skincare routine.)
All right.
How refreshing.
- Is that for hair loss? - Is that for the scalp?
What is that?
It prevents the top of my head from smelling.
The top...
When my scalp smells bad even after a shower,
I apply this product to my scalp...
after drying my hair.
And it feels really cool.
I'm short.
So some people would be taller than me.
Then they could smell the top of my head.
I didn't want to be the stinky one.
I'm quite sensitive to scents.
- I am. - I have to care about it.
If we were at the same eye level, this wouldn't be a problem.
But they're always taller than me.
It keeps bothering me.
So I'm sensitive to scents.
That's an uncomfortable part of being short.
- I see. - That never crossed my mind.
(I won't smell now, right?)
(Sniffing)
- Were you checking it? - I was.
- You were checking it. - Two fingers went in your nostril.
- I was checking. - Yes.
(Coughing)
(Even when she's sick, she gets started on laundry.)
- Oh, no. She's coughing. - Goodness.
You're sick. Shouldn't you rest?
But I had to do it.
With the laundry...
I would lie down if I were her.
I guess she had to do it no matter what.
(She stays busy without taking a break.)
(She runs the laundry.)
I live alone.
If I don't do it, who's going to do this?
- Right. That's true. - I'll have to do it.
- More chores would pile up. - Yes.
(She lets her clothes get washed.)
(Rummaging through)
(A cleaning towel?)
(She comes back to the bathroom.)
Okay.
(Grabbing)
(Spraying)
That's for washing your feet, right?
- Right. So... Yes. - The foot shampoo?
That's really effective.
And then I add toothpaste to it.
- Toothpaste? - Toothpaste?
(She mixes up a new kind of cleaning detergent.)
(She wets the brush with it and scrubs the toilet hard.)
Toothpaste is great at removing water stains.
It's good for water stains.
- You also see pink stains. - Right.
Toothpaste is good at removing those.
I clean the toilet every single time after I go.
I clean it right after going number two.
Every single time?
Yes, right after I go number two.
That's the cause of bad smells.
The thing I hate the most is walking into the bathroom...
and smelling the stink.
If I decide to rest today,
who will do the chores tomorrow? I'll have to.
It's not like I'll suddenly recover tomorrow.
I must do my chores.
- That's true. - Yes.
My grandmother raised me.
She'd say, "Oh, this is killing me." But she'd work on the farm.
She still cooked and did laundry. She did everything for me.
I grew up watching her.
So I get things done.
(So I get things done.)
My grandmother was the perfect example...
that showed how I ought to live my life.
What if this happens?
What if you have to go again after cleaning it?
Then I must clean it again.
- She's so diligent. - I must clean it again.
- But if it's part of your routine, - That must be frustrating.
This is nothing.
Has this ever happened before?
Have you ever tried to hold it to avoid cleaning the toilet?
No. It must come out.
- And... - But...
I might think about holding it in the middle of the night.
I have...
- Do you have a guest bathroom? - a guest bathroom.
After I clean my toilet,
I also clean the toilet in there once they leave.
I don't think I can visit your house because I'd feel bad.
- Same here. - They'll feel so uncomfortable.
- I'll feel bad using the toilet. - So...
So people barely come over.
Even if I'm at her house, I'd lie.
That I didn't use the toilet.
I wouldn't be comfortable telling her I used the toilet.
- I should bring my own poop bag. - Seriously.
- A poop bag? That sounds good. - A poop bag.
- You'll bring your own poop bag? - A poop bag?
- Are you serious? - Really?
Today's theme is dogs.
(A clean toilet that would make her guests feel uncomfortable)
(Shining)
I gently pour the water.
I see. She has to keep the floor dry.
- So you can't splash water. - Right.
Not to get the floor wet?
(She carefully rinses the toilet due to the dry floor.)
No one's going to visit your house.
They'd be scared to make a mess.
(She sprays the foot shampoo again after cleaning the toilet.)
What's that now?
Is that the mixture you made earlier?
Right. The first mixture was for the toilet.
The second mixture in another basket is for something else.
(She dunks the cleaning towel into the secret detergent.)
(It goes straight to the basin.)
(Scrubbing away and working up a sweat)
(Thoroughly wiping down the faucet)
(Scrubbing)
The bathtub.
(After cleaning the basin, she cleans the tub, shower booth, )
(and the toilet.)
(She makes sure to clean every corner.)
- They're back. - They're back.
- Oompa-Loompas. - Today,
- they're working in the bathroom. - Oompa-Loompas.
Right.
(Working as a cleaning crew today)
Aren't you pushing yourself too hard?
- No. - How could she be so thorough?
I doubt even professional cleaners would be this thorough.
All right.
(She washes the cleaning towel too.)
(Making sure the final cleanup is spotless too)
Gosh, it's hot.
- She's going to wipe the faucet. - That's the drying towel.
That's crazy.
I mean, look at the cabinet mirror.
- Yes. - It's spotless.
- Right. - There isn't a single waterdrop.
There's no window in the bathroom.
(There's no window.)
- Right. There's no window. - No.
Since there's no window,
I must ventilate it.
Even if it gets a tiny bit humid, the bathroom gets moldy.
It could easily get moldy.
So even if it's a hassle, I deep-clean my bathroom...
two or three times a week.
I remove moisture every day.
That's why I don't turn on the light in the bathroom.
I'd see the mold then.
- What? - What?
- I'm serious. - You keep the lights off?
Yes. I'd see the mold and stains.
- So I choose not to see them. - But...
That's the cause of throat infections.
Really?
Really? That's not good then.
(She scrubs thoroughly, so it doesn't get moldy...)
(and she can prevent throat infections.)
Her toilet bowl looks like white porcelain.
Right, it is.
You could even wash your face with the toilet water.
- A long time ago... - It's that clean.
(It shines as brightly as white porcelain.)
(Scrubbing every inch of the bathroom with all her effort)
- This is crazy. - Oh, her back must ache.
I mean, this is also part of my house.
(So she makes sure it's spotless.)
I'm done.
I finished.
- You said you were sick. - I hope she gets some rest.
I'll feel worse if I don't do anything because I'm sick.
(She takes a sip of the water.)
(Rustling)
(Tearing it open)
I make sure to take it on time.
(Taking the medicine for the throat infection)
(Coughing)
People cough like that when the infection is at its worst.
- Like the morning cough. - Right.
(She drinks the medicinal syrup too.)
(I'm all alone. I ought to recover fast.)
(Coughing)
- You don't even have phlegm then. - Right, no phlegm.
- It's impossible to hold it. - Right.
(Coughing)
(Her sick body feels even more tired after a deep-cleaning session.)
(She keeps on coughing.)
- Oh, no. - Gosh.
(Worried)
(She goes somewhere while coughing nonstop.)
(She goes straight to the door.)
- What's going on? - It's open.
(What bag is this?)
She must have ordered food.
She should. She's sick.
(Let me take them out of the bag.)
(A mysterious insulated bag)
- Strawberries. - Strawberries.
(She takes out sweet and sour strawberries.)
(Grabbing the strawberry box)
(She starts washing them immediately.)
I need vitamins to strengthen my immune system.
- I see. Right. - Yes.
(She places the rinsed strawberries in the bowl.)
(She also pops one in her mouth.)
(And she pops in another.)
- But I do the same thing. - Right.
- I can't be patient. - Right. Who can be patient?
My sense of taste started to get dull.
So I had to keep stimulating it with new food.
(She places 1 in the bowl and pops 1 in her mouth.)
(She keeps on eating strawberries while rinsing them.)
So when I was young,
I used to wonder why my mom only gave me the fruits...
- and didn't eat them. - Right.
- Moms eat more fruits than us. - Right.
(He finally finds out his mother's secret.)
She must already have eaten them.
When moms say they're full,
- They're serious. - they're serious.
"Watching you eat makes me full."
(They mean it 100 percent.)
- That's a fact. - Yes.
(After she finishes washing the tasty strawberries, )
(she brings something out.)
What's that?
- That's rice syrup. - Rice syrup.
(Finishing off with an elegant lick)
(She puts it back right away.)
(She takes out the gold spoon.)
(Crushing)
(Crushing mercilessly)
Why is she crushing them?
(As careful as she was during cleaning)
(Sniffling)
(Coughing)
(She sits on the sofa with the crushed strawberries.)
(She mixes them well.)
She eats them right away.
(What's this?)
(Why is she eating strawberries out of a bowl?)
It's medicine.
I don't eat it for taste.
It's a folk remedy that has been passed down...
from my Cheongdo grandma.
- Really? - I see.
- It's true. - I see.
Whenever I caught a cold,
she gave me this so that it'd pass from sweetness.
It has vitamins, sugar,
and throat-strengthening properties.
I eat it without fail when I catch a cold.
It's much tastier than strawberry syrup.
When you catch a cold,
they give you medicine in strawberry syrup flavor.
- You might be onto something. - Of course.
I wondered why it was strawberry-flavored.
To me, it's something like restorative herb medicine.
(To Shin Young, it's something like restorative herb medicine.)
(Slurping)
(Slurping in a satisfying way)
It isn't gomtang, is it?
My goodness.
- I mean... - For goodness' sake.
They're using a clip of him again!
(They're using a clip of him again!)
He appears each time.
(Drinking like it's soup)
(Drinking with her face buried in the bowl)
- She is really enjoying it. - I know.
(She gathers the last bits.)
- It must be delicious. - The last soup must be tasty.
It cures any sickness.
(That was nice.)
Seriously.
(She clears the bowl.)
(After finishing the strawberry medicine, )
(she goes back into the kitchen.)
It was tasty.
(My goodness)
(Even though she is sick, she washes the bowl right away.)
It's best to do the dishes right away.
Omija tea.
(Grabbing a bowl of rice)
What you ate was an appetizer.
(Now comes the real deal.)
Now comes the main dish.
Strawberries are just medicine.
- I took my medicine. - You took a sack of medicine.
Seriously.
(You took a sack of medicine.)
Let's do that.
(She puts it inside the microwave to thaw.)
(She naturally heads over to the fridge next to her.)
(Rummaging)
(Her hands are full of food items.)
- Stir-fried anchovies? - Stir-fried anchovies.
Yes. Stir-fried anchovies.
It's my first time seeing such a big amount of the dish.
I know.
During the holidays,
- you get many nuts as a gift. - That's right.
- We get them as a gift, - Yes.
- but we can't eat them regularly. - We don't eat them.
So I use them for stir-fried anchovies.
Nuts inside stir-fried anchovies are tasty.
(This time, she takes out the thawed rice.)
(She puts it in the metal bowl.)
She puts everything in the metal bowl.
(She opens the gigantic container of stir-fried anchovies...)
(and pours the dish over rice.)
(She mixes the ingredients after adding a lot of anchovies.)
It's half rice, half anchovies.
It'll be tasty as it is.
That's right. You shouldn't add anything else.
I agree. That's perfect.
- That's just right. - Exactly. You use your hands.
(That's good. I'm done mixing the ingredients.)
(Setting up dried laver in a corner)
(Then she covers the anchovy rice...)
(with dried laver.)
(Eating)
- It's tasty. - Stir-fried anchovies must be good.
Since I'm sick, I need to eat rice.
Most people with a throat infection lose their appetite.
You should eat when you're sick.
(Koreans get their energy from rice!)
(Impressed)
It must be good.
(Eating from time to time, )
(Shin Young piles up...)
(her anchovy gimbap.)
(Eating the remaining dried laver)
(She gathers the remaining rice...)
(and eats it in one bite.)
It's unbelievable that she cooks when she is sick.
I know.
So I brought some.
- Are you serious? - Yes.
- Really? - I want to try it.
- I want it. - I brought some.
Really?
- No way. - Thank you.
Hold on. Stay here.
(Stay here.)
(Oh, my!)
- The dried laver is big. - I mean...
- I mean... - It looks so tasty.
I shouldn't have eaten before the shoot.
- No way! - It looks good.
- Once it's mixed... - This is the setup.
- There is instant rice. - This is...
- It looks good. - stir-fried anchovies you saw.
- This is sudden. - It's mine.
It looks tasty.
You stir-fried nuts and anchovies.
I'll feed you guys...
- one at a time. - Will you feed us?
Of course.
(They just need to eat the anchovy gimbap.)
- She is like an auntie. - I know. This is so sudden.
- She'll scold us if we try to help. - I know.
- Exactly. - Stay put.
- We need to stay put. - Don't do anything. Stay put.
- Staying put is helping. - Stay put.
- To one bowl of rice... - Yes.
How much will you add?
When there is one bowl of rice, you should add this much.
- About half? - Yes.
- It smells so good. - You add a lot.
- That's a lot. - Here.
Combined, they'll be the size of a yellow corvina.
- I see more anchovies than rice. - The ratio is 1 to 1.
The ratio is 1 to 1.
- It looks tasty. - We'll get a bite each.
It's nutritious too.
- Yes, it is. - Yes.
(Once it's wrapped in dried laver, it's done.)
- Firstly... - Hyun Moo, you should go first.
- Here. - Hyun Moo, you should go first.
Here. Eat first.
(She delivers it to Moomoo's mouth first.)
Isn't it good?
- I told you so. - How is it?
It's tasty. It isn't very salty.
- I see. - Isn't it very salty?
I like that it isn't very salty.
- It's mildly seasoned. - It's mildly seasoned.
Eat it.
If stir-fried anchovies are too sweet or too salty,
- you get fed up with them. - It's just right.
Open wide. There you go.
It's good.
- It's tasty! - Right?
It's my first time someone fed me this.
- Really? - Right?
No one has done it.
No one has fed me this.
(Here, Bum June.)
(Twitching)
No one has fed me this.
(Opening)
- All right. - I twitched.
- It's tasty. - It's so tasty.
(I thought it was my turn.)
I added a lot.
- It's like making sushi. - Open wide.
- Don't touch it. - Do you want one more?
- Is it tasty? - It's tasty.
- It's so savory. - I know.
You should eat one too. You made it.
Your stir-fried anchovies are the best.
Shin Young, thank you.
- It's tasty. - I enjoyed it.
- I enjoyed it. - Seriously.
Her stir-fried anchovies aren't salty or sweet.
I could eat a pot of rice this way.
It was so tasty.
(It was tasty.)
Your stir-fried anchovies are the tastiest.
- Really? - Yes.
They're perfect when you make a wrap...
- with dried laver. - They're just right.
(Heave-ho)
(She brings the TV into the kitchen to accompany her during a meal.)
(After setting up the TV)
(Entering stealthily)
- It's a new shift worker. - That's right.
I thought it was a ghost.
(Another Shin Young enters.)
(Pressing the remote control)
Lead-off man.
(Even when she is sick, baseball is a must.)
(Is she beginning to cook again?)
There is more.
It's an accompaniment. It isn't a main dish.
(I see!)
She has more ingredients than a snack bar.
Didn't you say that you were sick?
Exactly.
I mean...
(You should eat when you're sick.)
- Stir-fried fishcake? - What will she make?
She is clearing out the sea today.
(That's good.)
(She picks up the remaining fishcake.)
- You should eat it as it is. - That's right.
(She folds it in half.)
- That's it. It's the tastiest. - That's it.
I agree.
Everyone does it.
(Chopping)
- She does that while being sick. - Exactly.
- But she looks happy. - Yes.
Do I have a mole there?
- Hold on. - Where?
- I think it's an anchovy particle. - On my cheek.
I see.
It must be an anchovy eye.
Is it dried laver?
(A dried laver particle landed on her cheek.)
Oh, yes.
(With a mole on her cheek, )
(she finishes chopping the vegetables in no time.)
(This time, she opens a tub of gochujang.)
(Grabbing)
(She scrapes it and adds it to the metal bowl.)
(She eyeball measures the chili powder.)
(Soy sauce, )
(starch syrup, )
(and minced garlic get added.)
- What is she making? - Gochujang, chili powder...
- Tteokbokki? - Tteokbokki!
- Tteokbokki. - I see.
- It's a tteokbokki sauce. - It's my tteokbokki recipe.
When I was in elementary school,
an auntie sold tteokbokki across from the school.
When she quit,
she gave me the recipe since I ate so much tteokbokki.
- She gave you the recipe. - "Add this and that..."
- "at home." - She gave you the recipe.
- Do you still use that recipe? - Yes.
(Sucking)
(It's perfect.)
Nice.
It's so tasty.
It'll be the talk of the town.
When you're sick,
- you need to eat spicy food. - Right.
- It makes you sweat. - Sweating helps.
(The chopped vegetables go into the pot first.)
(Then she mixes in the sauce.)
You cook like you're at a restaurant even though you're at home.
- Yes. - Right?
(While flavors seep into the vegetable broth)
It looks so tasty.
(Cutting)
(She prepares the main ingredient, rice cake, this time.)
Let's see.
(Long)
- They're so long. - Yes.
It's my specialty.
People slurp noodles, but not tteokbokki.
But I slice all the ingredients into long strips...
so that I can eat them in one bite.
- Will you slurp the fishcake? - Yes.
At first, I used regular wheat flour rice cake.
Then I began cutting the pieces in half.
I cut them so that they'd be long.
But recently, I found out about the long rice cake.
It was a eureka moment.
I must slurp for every meal.
That's my routine for living right.
It's a great saying.
(Rinsing)
(She rinses the long wheat flour rice cake.)
I should've done that.
(She adds the long fishcake she has sliced.)
(It looks delicious already.)
It looks good.
I didn't know you could get that color at home.
You get that color when you use rice syrup.
It would be nice with the anchovy gimbap.
- Yes. It's the best combination. - It would be amazing.
- She left some behind for that. - That's right.
But it isn't a leftover. It's what I prepared.
(It isn't a leftover. It's what I prepared.)
- Really? - Yes.
- It isn't a leftover. No. - I thought you were done eating.
I simply ate as I made the dish.
I see why moms can't lose weight.
Moms do that.
- That's so funny. - It's a secret.
I see.
(Opening)
What's that?
(A familiar-looking container?)
The treasure box of my heart.
- I see. Glass noodle container? - Glass noodles.
Yes. It's a glass noodle container.
- Will you add glass noodles again? - A glass noodle container.
(She eats glass noodles for every meal.)
(I guess she adds them whenever the dish has some soup.)
(Glass noodles are a must for the soupy tteokbokki.)
She couldn't hold back upon seeing the soup.
They're essential.
(Opening)
(Shin Young's soaked jewels)
Look at the soaked glass noodles. How detailed.
(She carefully removes the water.)
(She adds a handful of glass noodles.)
(Lastly, it's time to add the rice cake.)
Let's add the rice cake.
You aren't watching baseball today as always.
- I'm watching. I'm listening. - Are you listening?
(Sucking in a breath)
(I'm salivating.)
It's done. It's finished.
(Shin Young's long tteokbokki with glass noodles is complete.)
- Look at that. - It makes me clap.
I wish there were a snack bar that sold the same tteokbokki.
Come to my place.
I won't go.
(Feeling pressured)
I don't care about pooping or creating a mess.
I clean up when the guests leave.
- I don't make the guests... - But I'll worry about it.
- Her house will be like torture. - Why?
You're bound to poop when you eat that much.
- I'll poop at a shopping center. - That's right.
- I'll feel so bad on my way home. - Seriously.
Since I'm sick, I'll eat a bit more.
(Since she is sick, she takes one handful.)
(She takes two handfuls.)
I'll get some rice cake.
(The third handful is the last one.)
That's a lot.
(This is enough.)
- She adds pepper even in there. - That's right.
(Sprinkling pepper)
That's right.
- That's incredible. - Seriously.
You see that color in tteokbokki...
- only in front of a girls' high. - That's right.
- You're right. Not a boys' high. - Definitely not a boys' high.
Boys aren't picky.
That's right. I agree.
(Humming)
(She takes out another plate.)
All right.
- Pickled radish. - There is so much.
- Why are you getting so much? - It's a whole plate.
She emptied the container.
All right.
(She rushes over to eat.)
(She takes off her glasses to begin eating in earnest.)
(Blowing)
(Slurping)
How nice.
It looks tasty.
(She picks up the rice cake, fishcake, and glass noodles.)
(She slurps the three ingredients.)
It's tasty.
(Her eyes go wide.)
- You aren't crying, are you? - How touching.
It made me cry.
(Slurping)
The sound is insane.
- It looks so tasty. - It looks unbelievably tasty.
(She inhales the food without missing anything.)
(Ecstatic)
Look at that.
(Shaking her head)
- Look at that. - Are you gnawing on a rib?
- Hold on. What's that? - She is a lion.
Am I a seal or what? Hold on.
It's so funny. You eat like this.
- You're like a seal. - Like someone who was never sick.
Gosh, it's spicy.
(She restores her energy fully.)
Let's put pickled radish on the top.
(She puts pickled radish on the top.)
(My goodness)
- I love the thin pickled radish. - That's right.
- You know what's good, Bum June. - Yes.
My nose is runny.
(Grabbing)
(Sweat rolls down her face.)
Invigorating food is what you enjoy.
It's what makes you sweat.
People's idea of invigorating food is...
duck meat. It's tasty.
Samgyetang is tasty as well. All of those are tasty.
But I must add glass noodles. I must eat them once a day.
I must slurp them.
Invigorating food is what you enjoy the most. Seriously.
(Slurping fast)
(She becomes absorbed in eating her invigorating food.)
Watch the baseball game, will you?
(I forgot about that.)
- You didn't watch for a second. - I listened.
- I watched like this. - Don't be ridiculous.
- Last time, - I watched like this.
She was self-conscious enough...
to glance over at the TV as she put food in her mouth.
She isn't even listening this time.
- I'm watching the game. - Not at all.
She won't notice it if someone turns off the TV.
- I'm watching the game. - For goodness' sake.
- This is insane. - Also,
there is the anchovy gimbap.
- It's the best. - It should be eaten together.
(She eats it in one go.)
It looks so tasty.
(This is nice.)
(Wiping the table)
(She pushes food around instead of eating.)
Gosh, it's spicy.
It's a bit spicy.
(Why is she getting up?)
Will she get more?
With the excuse of the food being too spicy...
She'll add something.
I'll eat more later.
(To be continued)
(Is Shin Young leaving food behind?)
I'll eat more later.
I stopped then and there.
- You know how to stop. - I left food behind.
(The glass noodle factory stops running for the first time.)
(Feeling troubled)
This happens maybe three times a year.
When I have a cold...
with a runny nose or bronchitis,
I can't taste the flavors.
At first, the food is tasty.
But the fever makes the inside of the nose swell.
When that happens, I can't taste anything.
That's when I put down the spoon.
I do it with determination.
When my nose is stuffy, I can't taste the food.
But you've eaten enough.
(Really?)
You ate strawberries too.
(Despite having swollen nasal passages, )
(she eats enough and goes to the sink.)
She is neat.
(She cleans up right away even when she is sick.)
Shin Young never throws food out.
I never throw food out.
Let's see.
(Sighing)
(The side dish container is way up there.)
I had to put in the leftover tteokbokki,
but it was way up there.
I see. You must've never had any leftovers until now.
(Let's go up.)
Heave-ho!
(Slipping)
Gosh, I almost died.
- That moment... - Gosh, my shin hurts!
- Gosh! - Gosh, I almost died.
- She stopped herself from cursing. - "I almost died."
It was just a groan.
(She tries again after swallowing the harsh words.)
Be careful!
(She manages to go up and takes out the side dish container.)
(Hopping)
(A short and impressive celebration)
There we go.
(She puts the tteokbokki into the container.)
I can have that again in the morning.
It's really good. It's like it was freshly made.
(The tteokbokki gets stored in the refrigerator.)
How can you do that when you're sick?
- I did feel really sick. - How neat!
- Gosh! - No way.
But I'm the only one that can take care of everything.
(She walks over to the living room after cleaning up.)
(Pressing the remote control)
(Coughing)
(She turns on the baseball again while coughing.)
At that moment,
I thought I had a fractured rib.
- It was that bad? - Right.
- Your stomach cramps up. - Right.
(Rummaging)
She's taking something out!
The sweet potato chips?
(Fried fish meat)
It's something different.
- Right! - Did you finish the chips?
She must've finished the sweet potato chips.
(Is she covering her mouth?)
(She covered her mouth while having the sweet potato chips...)
(to prevent the crumbs from falling.)
(She's covering her mouth once again today as she eats.)
What's the difference between you being sick and not being sick?
- I couldn't finish the tteokbokki! - Gosh.
Around two minutes ago, she said her nose felt numb.
I can't taste the flavors.
(Is she free from her numbness after 2 minutes?)
(Rattling)
- What's going on? - I had to brush off my hands.
(She brushes off her hands inside the packet.)
(I must protect my sofa at all costs.)
I closed it up after just a few bites.
That never happens.
(Look at that.)
(Clearing her throat)
(Coughing)
It must be really painful.
There's a throbbing pain inside.
My legs went up because of the pain.
It's severe.
Gosh.
This is bad. My throat hurts so much.
(She heads to the kitchen while continuing to cough.)
Gosh.
Gosh, I got a bad cold.
(She got something out from the refrigerator.)
What is it this time?
Gosh, it hurts so much.
(A bowl of ice cream)
- It's a bowl of ice cream. - Right.
It seems like you're coughing hard to eat something.
Why would I do that?
Come on. I'm really sick.
(She takes out the metal bowl again.)
- Why the metal bowl? - Why does it keep appearing?
You're eating with the metal bowl all day long!
How many metal bowls do you have?
You might develop hyperlipidemia! Be careful.
The whole bowl is taken out?
No!
That's high in calories.
(The whole bowl of ice cream is taken out.)
When one gets tonsillitis...
or a cold,
mothers give ice cream.
It's for the fever.
The fever is brought down with the ice cream.
It's a tonic.
- That's a no. - It was because I was sick.
(Being brazen)
(Shall I start putting together the tonic?)
(Opening)
(Potato chips?)
(Crushing)
Really? Potato chips on ice cream?
- It's really good. - Right.
Gosh, being sick makes me crave these things.
Won't that scratch up the roof of your mouth?
No. It's okay, as it was mashed up finely.
All right. Shall I dig in?
I will start eating in earnest.
She's eating really well as someone who is sick.
I had to feed myself well. Who will take care of me?
(She takes a bite of the tonic she put together for herself.)
Gosh.
(My goodness. This was what I wanted.)
(Is she sniffling?)
(She rolls a big scoop with her wrist.)
(She shoves it in after opening up her throat.)
It was the best.
Gosh, it's good.
(I feel much better.)
(She scoops another bite with the crunchy potato chips.)
As it went down my throat,
it soothed my swollen throat and salivary glands.
- It brought everything down. - That's right.
I'm eating it to get better.
When I have tonsillitis or am feeling sick,
having something smooth will...
- That's enough. - Right.
- I'm serious. - Stop trying to connect...
to your illness.
I'm serious! I was actually sick!
She's saying so many groundless things.
Gosh.
My throat doesn't hurt now.
(She brought down her throat infection...)
(with half a bowl of ice cream.)
(Grabbing the tissue)
(Getting up)
(Grabbing)
(She has leftovers again?)
(She covers it up diligently with the plastic wrap.)
(It gets stored in the refrigerator just like the tteokbokki.)
I wasn't able to finish it as I was sick.
(I wasn't able to finish it as I was sick.)
(Coughing)
(She takes out a bunch of dried laundry.)
She gets everything done even though she's sick.
Things like the laundry...
- They must be done quickly. - can't get pushed back.
(I must fold the laundry even though I'm sick.)
(Heave-ho!)
(Let's see.)
(She folds it nicely into three equal parts.)
Do you fold your socks like that?
Yes. Always.
(Throwing into the basket)
(Sniffling)
Gosh, the rhinitis looks bad.
- Right. - Gosh.
I felt so sick at that time.
(She folds it neatly even while sniffling.)
- Like that. - I also fold the towel like that.
- Right. Like a ball. - Right.
(Sniffling)
(She works diligently even when she's in bad condition.)
(I'm done.)
(Heave-ho!)
(The folded laundry gets put back in.)
Gosh.
(That's amazing.)
Gosh, it's like a hotel!
Gosh, I'm done now.
You're done now. Get some rest.
(Coughing)
(Rustling)
(She puts a piece of candy into her mouth.)
(Lying down)
She's lying down for the first time.
(She finally lies down after getting the house chores done.)
Let's watch together.
How cute.
They have similar heights.
(They're just like each other.)
What are you saying?
(A sense of comfort from a similar height)
(She covers herself with a cozy blanket as well.)
Support my team.
(Support my team, Wilson.)
It feels sad to be sick,
but it feels worse to be lazy.
There's no need for crying. It's a waste of tissues.
If I'm focused on feeling pity from my sickness,
I turn into the most miserable person in the world.
- Right. - It just feels miserable.
Who will wash my socks?
Sad Shin Young has to wash them.
Instead of being like that, I think realistically now.
We have to live on.
We should take medicine if we feel sick.
We should get an IV drip if we feel really sick.
We should get an injection on the bottom.
We must carry on with life.
Those who feel sad must see things realistically.
I think it's right about feeling worse to be lazy.
We've all been through this. When we were students,
we said, "I feel so sick. May I go to the nurse's office?"
We went to the nurse's office just like that.
Let's say I was filming for a show, and I said,
"May I go to the nurse's office?"
"Career over."
"I feel awful. I want to go home."
(Career over)
"She has a crazy personality!"
"Kim Shin Young leaves during show."
"Will she be able to carry on?" People will say these things.
I must be 100 percent responsible for myself.
Being sick is fine.
Anyone can get sick.
Adding in feelings, fantasies,
and sorrow? There's no time for that.
Anyone can catch a cold.
Colds will go away in the end.
Colds are things that can get treated.
You will get better.
I went to see the doctor on Sunday.
There were 40 people waiting in line after me.
They were all sick.
They all came to see the doctor on their own.
While shedding tears at home alone,
I can't say, "I feel so sick. Come and see me."
I can see a doctor instead of doing that.
Nobody cries at this age.
Nobody screams their head off while getting a shot on their bottom.
If I scream at the age of 44,
people will say, "She's insane. What's wrong with her?"
"Kim Shin Young is a lunatic."
"She's screaming her head off."
Someone will write those kinds of comments. That can't happen.
I have to endure everything as I'm an adult.
That's being ridiculous at my age.
That can't happen.
I must live gallantly with both feet on the ground.
I have to stay alert when I feel sick.
I must grind myself until the end.
That's impressive.
I must move to live while I'm feeling sick.
- Right. - Right.
(Blinking)
(Snoring)
(Shin Young crashes out after the exhausting day.)
(Gosh!)
(Embarrassed)
(She falls asleep again.)
(Gallantly Riding Out Alone)
(I Live Alone)
It's Dowoon.
All right. Why are you clapping?
- Sorry? - What was that about?
What's wrong?
(Running?)
(That will never happen again in my life.)
(Dowoon left a significant message after the Fun Run.)
I had a lot of fun.
- What was that about? - What's wrong?
Where would I go?
- Are you sure? - Yes.
The Fun Run was amazing!
"The Fun Run was amazing!"
That can be his last Fun Run.
I'm planning to make him come for a real run.
He will never do a real run.
What do you think about a real run?
I love both of them.
Running is just...
(Smirking)
Dowoon is more toward my side.
Dowoon and Na Ra are more toward my side.
I won't try to take Na Ra.
- Just... - Why are you trying to take Dowoon?
Let Dowoon come to my side.
- He's trying to go against us. - That's not it.
I have to show people the joy of a real run.
The Fun Run has a lot more content.
Right.
There's food, traveling,
- You've really chosen that path. - and there's talking.
I would join the Fun Run as well.
There's drawing as well.
- The real run is just running. - Right.
It's just about setting records.
I should get myself prepared.
All right. Here's a member who is about to join the second Fun Run.
- Let's watch Joy's clip. - The Fun Run?
(Let's watch Joy's clip.)
He relates everything to the Fun Run.
(Enjoy the New Journey!)
- "Enjoy!" - "Enjoy!"
(Joy heads somewhere.)
There are so many things to see.
(Walking)
Gosh, it's so cute!
(Gosh, it's so cute!)
So this is it.
This is it.
(She even takes a picture.)
Where is this?
(The place she came to with a heart full of excitement)
(Cheonho Stationery and Toy Street)
- The Stationery Street? - There's a place like this?
This is Cheonho-dong's Stationery Street.
(Cheonho Stationery and Toy Street)
So there's a place like that.
The Stationery Street is really hot these days.
- Really? - Yes.
(The place is filled with stationery and toys.)
It's been a while since I've seen a stationery store like that.
(Including various kinds of stationery...)
The Stationery and Toy Street...
- in Dongmyo is famous. - Right.
Some of the owners who were there moved over to this area.
That was how a new one was formed in Cheonho-dong.
I'm about to make a big challenge this year.
I have to study really hard.
As I'm someone who finds working tools to be important,
I came to this place to prepare myself...
with the right supplies.
Supplies are important.
- Hello. - Hello.
Where is the stationery?
They're over there.
I see.
I can imagine how that place smells.
That particular smell of that store.
Right.
- Stationery stores smell nice. - Right.
(After diligently checking the writing supplies, )
(she puts in the pens she likes.)
(She walks inside.)
What?
(Prepared mustard)
- "Prepared mustard?" - "Mustard?"
Is it an eraser?
- It's a highlighter. - A highlighter?
- A highlighter of that color? - Yes.
- There are many fascinating items. - There are so many of them.
(She loves it.)
I like this.
(Will this one be better?)
"Cramming from now on."
It's targeted toward those who don't study.
- Right. - Right.
- The studious ones... - Right?
Are studying instead of going to places like that.
- Right. - They also use classic pens.
- Right. - Right.
They have just what they need.
I should get this one.
(She puts in the highlighter that doesn't look classic at all.)
There were highlighters here as well.
(She picks up another handful of highlighters.)
(I must get notebooks as well.)
That's the most exciting moment.
Buying notebooks before the new semester.
"This one is for Korean."
- Right. - "This one is for English."
Your name is written on the side.
- Right. After spreading it out. - Your name is written like that.
That affection lasts a month.
- Right. - Right.
- You get sick of it later. - Right.
You forget where the notebook has gone later on.
(Taking a look)
There are more squishies.
(Squishies?)
Squishies!
I love squishies.
The slime was popular for a while.
The squishy has the same texture of the slime,
but there's an extra layer on the outside.
It doesn't stick to your hand.
(The squishy can be carried around and played with.)
Doesn't it feel nice just to see it?
It's a stress-reliever.
- There are pet squishies. - Pet squishies?
There are a lot of people who carry those around.
I'm someone who is trend-sensitive.
That's why I've started collecting squishies recently.
- So people collect those. - So that's in trend right now.
They're really popular. Why don't you know them?
- I know them. - You're no longer the TSM.
You didn't even listen to my answer.
I know what squishies are.
I was worried that...
- they would get dirty after use. - I see.
You can squish your face.
The Mooshy.
(Hesitating)
(I want to get a squishy.)
I'm here to buy stationery.
(Let's get to my senses.)
(She focuses on buying stationery after feeling tempted.)
There are more squishies here!
It's a potato.
(Squishing)
- It's the potato bun! - That one is cute.
(Eyes rolling)
(It goes into the basket.)
Gosh. I like all of them.
It's those times when I feel like a successful adult.
- I keep getting reminded... - Right.
- Right. - of my childhood.
(Chuckling)
(She spots a squishy that is shaped like a face.)
- What is that? - What is that?
It looks like someone.
It looks...
(Looking closely)
a bit like Jun Hyun Moo.
(It looks like Jun Hyun Moo.)
(Even the Mooshy gets put into the basket.)
- I ended up buying so many things. - That's a lot of things.
(She finally heads to the counter!)
(The basket is filled with toys instead of stationery.)
- There are so many of them. - There are so many of them.
I ended up buying so many of them.
I've been trying to live like a minimalist.
- What are you saying? - I'm serious!
I shared the things I had...
and refrained from buying things.
But I couldn't stop myself from buying the squishies.
They might end up being sold at the bazaar.
They're going to appear without being opened.
That is how we get a lot of things at the bazaar.
- I got it now. - Right.
(The loaded basket gets checked out.)
You've bought a lot of different things.
(Feeling proud)
One of these.
(The squishies get checked out endlessly.)
- You must be a big spender. - Right.
The maximalist.
- Gosh. - Here's the receipt.
I bought so many things.
She's living her dream.
- Thank you. - People like her and me...
are making the economy flow.
(People like her and me are making the economy flow.)
(She successfully makes the economy flow.)
(Struggling)
(She feels great.)
(She arrives somewhere while humming.)
It's not her home.
- Hello. - Hi.
(Tapping)
Welcome, Ms. Park Soo Young.
- Can I keep this somewhere? - Sure.
- Give it to me. - Thank you.
(Striding inside after keeping her stuff)
- Please put on your name tag. - Okay.
(Behind Joy who settles herself naturally...)
This is a pet grooming school.
It's where you learn and train...
to get a pet groomer certification.
(Where she comes to study these days)
I started coming here as soon as...
my drama shoot was done.
I went to register myself the next day...
right after the drama wrap-up party.
It's been around two months.
(It's been 2 months since she started going to the school.)
I always think about what ifs.
"If I can't continue..."
"with this career,"
"how should I live on?" I had such a thought.
I thought it'd be nice to have some sort of skills.
Since I love dogs,
I decided to learn pet grooming.
That's how I started this.
Isn't it helpful in real life too?
Yes, I can groom my dog too.
It's good for dog shelter volunteering too.
The chance of getting adopted...
- That's right. - goes up high.
- That's a good thing. - If you groom them a bit...
- I wanted to do the volunteering. - Totally.
There are written and practical exams.
The number of times you can take them...
is four only.
There's a written exam in July.
First, to prepare for the practical exam,
I've been going there 10 times within 2 months to learn.
(A shapeless white fluff ball)
She worked hard.
(She started learning to cut it in a heart shape.)
(After a long practice, )
(Joy managed to turn it into a dog shape.)
It's learning to make a poodle shape.
Making a poodle is a practical exam.
There are 1st-stage grooming and 2nd-stage grooming.
- As for 1st-stage... - You need a 1st-stage grooming?
You need to brush and straighten...
the white fluff ball at first.
Then you do the first-stage grooming.
Then you do the second stage, which is shaping the fur.
You need to finish the whole process...
within two and a half hours during the exam.
But it took me 6 hours for the 1st-stage grooming.
I did 2nd-stage grooming for 5 hours the day before.
That day, I went to wrap up.
Since you're done with the 1st and 2nd-stage grooming,
- Yes. Okay. - you'll do the tail and ears today.
Good luck.
(Good luck to me.)
- I think you'll complete it today. - Okay.
(Quickly taking out the tools)
(Ready to practice grooming)
It looks like...
- I've trimmed it a lot. - Yes.
- But it's far from done. - Isn't that good already?
No, I'm far from done.
- It looks like a real dog. - Yes.
It looks like a living dog.
(Let's see.)
From here...
(She takes a quick look and cuts it.)
(She's quite skilled with scissors...)
(as she's been practicing for two months.)
It's fun.
When I'm practicing grooming,
it feels like an hour has passed,
but four hours have been gone.
(She continues grooming with scissors with one hand.)
You have to hold the nose of it.
Just now,
- you held scissors with one hand... - Yes.
- and a brush with another, right? - Yes.
(Joy used the scissors with one hand earlier.)
- You can't do that, can you? - Right.
- She's so scary. - Right.
You must hold the nose with the other hand.
- You must do that. It's dangerous. - That's right.
That's how a teacher should be like.
That way, you learn faster.
- Otherwise, a dog could get hurt. - Here's why you hold the snout.
- A dog could fall off the table. - Right.
If it falls, then you're disqualified.
- So always hold the snout, - Yes.
- Yes. - and fix it.
You must always hold the snout.
What if it bites?
What if it goes like this?
- You use a real dog for the exam? - No.
- We use that for the exam too. - Right. That doesn't make sense.
(Joy got feedback from the instructor.)
(Let me try it again.)
There you go.
(Holding the snout first as the instructor told her)
- It's hard. - This isn't easy.
- It must be hard. - Yes.
(She carefully continues grooming.)
(Glancing)
(The other classmates seem skilled.)
There are many male students too.
There are people of all ages and gender in the class.
- She's really good. - Yes.
- Goodness. - Gosh.
(She gets motivated and starts again with a new mindset.)
(Her back gets hunched more as time goes by.)
(In the end, she stands in a weird posture.)
The instructor told me I should stand like that.
That's cool. You look like an artist.
(Serious)
Gosh, her back must hurt.
Her back must hurt.
- Your back must hurt. - It really does.
My back and neck hurt so much.
(Now, she's almost crawling.)
The instructor is so scary.
(The instructor is watching her from afar.)
- She's so scary. - She must not like...
what you're doing.
(Staring quietly)
(Approaching)
That's the most nerve-racking.
- I've been watching you from afar. - Yes.
The name of the scissors is blades without movements.
- Yes. - So it has to be fixed.
But you are putting it close to the dog,
and moving like this without it touching the dog.
After that, the fur will keep sticking out...
- when you brush it. - Yes, it keeps doing that.
Right? That's because you pushed it down instead of cutting.
It's completely different...
- from normal trimming. - I can see that.
That kind of trimming is called fixed blades.
You must fix the top blade,
- and move with the down blade only. - You're right.
That's really hard.
So on the 1st day, I only practiced that trimming for 2 hours.
I practiced that only.
- Oh, like that? - Oh, that?
- You must fix the top blade. - It must make your hand numb.
It makes your hand numb. You get calluses here.
It's different from my way of grooming.
Sorry?
(Doubleblade84 cuts his hair with no order.)
I've been cutting my own hair for ten years.
(Feeling proud)
(Unlike Doubleblade84)
(she's grooming the dog with top blade fixed.)
Gosh, ma'am!
(Observing her from behind)
- She's a good instructor. - You should listen to her.
- You're right. - That's how one should be.
Gosh, it's tiring.
Ma'am, what should I do now?
I was startled.
Should I trim more?
(Coming close to Joy)
What is it?
She laughs too.
What you need to pay attention to...
- is scissors. - Yes.
You'll be trimming a real dog...
- in the future. - Yes.
It shouldn't be dangerous when you trim a real dog.
It'll be better if you fix the top blade a bit more.
- That must be really important. - Fixing the top blade.
If you don't want to hurt the dog...
Also, shake off the tail fur...
- as well. - Okay.
I'll teach you how to trim...
- the tail properly later. - Okay.
- It says "Fix the top blade..." - Yes.
In red on the wall.
- Yes, it's the most important. - It must be really important.
- It must be important. - Like a class motto.
- Right. - Look. "Fix the top blade."
- "Fix the top blade." - There's a competition on that too.
- Really? - Yes.
(Flopping)
(Gosh, I'm tired.)
(Taking a glance at other classmates)
I thought, "This is so tough,"
"but they're managing it?"
(They're all so good.)
Are you jealous?
(Glancing)
It took me a month to finish a dog.
- Really? - Yes.
I didn't know it was so hard before I began learning it.
You're pretty good, considering how it's your first time.
- She's so kind. - Right.
Really? I...
It gets better when you finish three.
It gets better if I finish three dogs?
You get better as your skills improve.
- Really? - If you finish this,
- you'll get the hang of it soon. - Yes.
Your skills improve.
I only got scolded today.
I kept getting scolded too.
When did I scold you?
She was listening.
(I didn't scold you.)
I was scolded quite a lot today too.
(Amicable)
It became really hairy when I brushed it.
- You're right. - That's the tail.
(Getting into it in earnest after boosting her confidence)
(Focused)
(Steady focus)
I practiced for two and a half hours that day.
(Model dog slowly taking shape)
The tail is cute!
It's like a balloon dog.
A dog made of balloon.
- Right. - I know.
A dog balloon.
You did a good job meeting the right size of the tail.
- As for the edges, - Yes.
You can trim it a bit.
You'll be done with it if you complete the tail.
- It'll be done finally? - You'll be done.
Great job.
It's Minky.
- It's pretty. - It's cute.
Minky is cute, right?
(She finally completed her first model dog.)
- Great job, really. - It's so tiring.
(A triumphant masterpiece)
Minky!
I hung my name tag.
- I'm so proud of it. - I got goosebumps.
Right.
I'm not happy with it.
Why not?
Gosh, seriously...
I clearly cut it nicely and well with scissors.
But when you brush it,
the hidden fur keeps coming out.
There was a big difference.
I tried my best to imitate it,
and I worked hard to follow.
It does look more condensed.
- That's neater. - You're right.
Joy's is more like a sheep.
- Right? - Dogs like that are cuter...
in real life.
- That's true. - They need to be lacking.
- That's right. It's too smooth. - Right.
It's really hard.
We often take our dogs to a groomer.
They should charge 1,000 dollars per dog.
- What are you talking about? - The value of labor.
I worked myself to the bone.
I poured my all, passion, and spirits into it.
(Cleaning up after completing her dog)
(Let's go, Minky.)
(Bumping)
- Oh, dear. - No. Minky's leg broke.
She's treating it horribly.
At that rate, its kneecap popped out.
No way.
- Thank you. - Sure.
- Great job. - Right. Thank you.
(Joy came outside.)
She must be exhausted.
The sun has set.
(Tired)
(The long-awaited taxi is here.)
- Hello. - Welcome.
(Squishing)
For peace of mind.
- Seriously. - There's a reason...
- why she bought that a lot. - Seriously.
I get her now.
(She passed out soon.)
- I was exhausted. - Seriously.
You're tired because you bought that much.
That's not true.
- Grooming was the hard part. - You went around a lot.
They'd think you're selling the squish balls.
(Joy became completely worn out...)
(after a two-and-a-half-hour grueling schedule.)
(She came home after an exhausting day.)
Look who's here?
(Barking)
Come here.
- My baby. - Oh, my.
My pretty baby.
It's my baby, Haetnim.
It's a female dog, and she's eight this year.
(Hi.)
- She's cute, right? - She's cute.
She's a dog raised at my parents' house,
but she comes to my place often.
She's a Maltese.
She's got the typical Maltese sass.
But she's really gentle.
She's really kind.
And she's a really pretty dog.
How cute.
(Doting on her)
I'm tired.
Haetnim, I'm tired.
(Joy passes out after a long training.)
I'm so tired.
(Knocked out in front of Haetnim)
Haetnim.
(I should get up.)
Haetnim, are you hungry?
(Yes!)
(She heads straight to the kitchen.)
Haetnim.
(I should feed Haetnim.)
(A special menu for Haetnim)
(Mine?)
She's so cute! She's waiting.
(Screaming)
Haetnim. What is this?
(Haetnim, let's eat.)
Come here, Haetnim.
You're here.
- What is this? - She's so cute.
- What is this? - How cute.
My princess only eats when I put it in my hand.
Here.
(Eating like a princess)
She's so cute.
You're eating well. Is it good?
You're so cute.
Hey.
Hey. You should have vegetables too.
- Don't only eat chicken. - She must be a picky eater.
- She's a picky eater. - She has no table manners.
She only picked out vegetables?
That's how we were like as kids.
We picked out spinach in gimbap.
Yes. She doesn't eat vegetables.
Why are you eating meat only?
(Gosh, I have no choice.)
(Taking something)
What's that?
Haetnim.
- Nose work toys? - They love that.
- It's Shin Ramyeon. - Oh, they take it out.
Come down, now.
Dogs love that.
Eat it in your spot, Princess.
Come here. Sit.
Touch.
Kiss.
- Touch. - Because she's a Maltese,
- She has a temper, right? - she has a temper.
- Touch. - She is about to get mad.
Get down!
Touch.
Get...
(Barking)
- High-five. - She does it for you, though.
She does everything.
High-five.
(Stop it.)
Wait.
(Carefully placing it on her legs)
She's waiting.
- She waits for you. - She's such a good dog.
She can't help it if she wants to eat.
You can eat it.
How cute!
- How cute! - Such a good dog.
- Go there. - She's a good dog.
How adorable.
How cute. She's so cute.
(Treats are the best.)
(Bringing something)
(The food she ordered in advance)
- You must've been starved. - Yes. I hadn't eaten anything.
(Hurry)
What is it?
(The brilliant mango bingsu)
I'm into mango bingsu these days.
You're not having a proper meal when you didn't eat anything.
Why are you having bingo? Oh, not bingo.
Bingo?
You shortened mango bingsu and called it bingo?
- It sounds like bingsu. - Why would she eat bingo?
(Having a bite of bingo for her first meal)
Mangoes are good these days.
- It's really good. - It's sweet.
It's so good.
I need to study.
(Taking something out)
What is it?
I need to pass the written exam...
to take the practical exam.
They told me I needed to study for the written exam by myself.
The written exam is in July,
and I'm studying for it right now.
(Shall I start studying now?)
(Turning it on)
You're already doomed by trying to study on the sofa.
You're right.
You can't sit there for too long because your back hurts.
Right. It's been long since I studied.
It's really fun when you watch TV then.
- You're right. - Anything is fun then.
- Right. - You tend to lie down right away.
(Putting down the remote control as though she's determined)
(Let's study for real.)
(Rustling)
I mean...
As she's about to study, other things...
- are starting to catch her eye. - That's right.
She needs to explore the stationery.
That's right. I needed to get ready first.
(Pouring)
She got so much stuff.
Oh, my gosh.
Why did I get so much stuff?
(A pile of toys poured in the living room)
(Getting up)
This is already full, though.
It's my squishy toy collection.
They're the selected ones.
Your forearm muscles must be strong.
But it does help with scissoring.
- That's true. - That's how they're related?
Yes.
This is the best.
(Thinking of scissoring, )
(she's immersed in exploring the squishy toys.)
How should I put it?
It feels like being inside a cloud.
When I touch it, it gives me peace of mind.
(Twitching)
You should start studying.
Joy.
(He couldn't hold back and starts nagging.)
(Grunting)
I don't want to study.
You haven't even started.
(But I should.)
The beginning is always the hardest.
You're so cute.
All right. Let's do it.
How am I supposed to memorize all these?
Right, Haetnim?
- What is this? - What's that?
I have to memorize all of them.
You must memorize all of them?
Cephalus.
Muzzle.
Shoulder point.
- They're all in Chinese words. - Shoulder point.
Right.
Upper arm.
Toes.
Armpit.
Gosh, how can I memorize them?
They're so hard.
You must memorize all of them.
(Overwhelmed)
(Grabbing)
I must use all means possible.
(Drawing)
The front part is the brainpan.
(Drawing herself to memorize instead of using the picture)
Muzzle. What was it again?
The muzzle.
You must get used to the Chinese words first.
- Right. - Number seven.
The nose. "Bi" is Chinese for nose.
Wait. What's muzzle and what's nose?
(Confused)
- What? - It's hard.
(It's hard to memorize even if she draws a picture herself.)
Haetnim, come here.
Let me see your nose.
I think it'll be better if you study with Haetnim.
This is a muzzle.
(Haetnim, help me.)
Cephalus. Brainpan.
Ears. Eyes.
Stop.
(Okay, I memorized them.)
(Let's move on to the next part.)
Gosh, what is this?
- The skeleton is even harder. - Oh, my gosh.
What is this?
The upper jawbone.
(She starts memorizing for now.)
The lower jawbone.
(She can't help but frown.)
- Sternum. - How can you memorize them?
Tell me about it!
There's a memorization genius.
Who?
He wrote a book about a miracle mnemonic method.
(The creator of miracle mnemonic method)
I use this a little...
- when I study a foreign language. - Right.
- I'll teach you. - Please do.
- Which word can't you memorize? - Muzzle.
Muzzle...
- When we take Kumon classes, - What is this?
Dogs always come.
- Mom would prepare fruits for us. - Right.
Then the dog wants to...
eat the fruit as well.
With the muzzle.
So the muzzle that wants to eat the fruit.
- Muzzle. - Muzzle.
That's right.
I don't think you'll have enough time during the exam.
That's true.
I'll just memorize them myself.
(Thank you, but I'll just memorize them myself.)
Cervical vertebra.
This is crazy. How can I memorize them?
(This is crazy. How can I memorize them?)
(When will I memorize all these?)
(But she grabs her pen again.)
This is so hard.
(Grunting)
(In the end, she stops studying.)
- I mean... - This is good exercise.
Haetnim, look at me.
Look at me.
(Pretending not to know)
This is so good.
(Breathing in and out)
The exam is in July, right?
(She has less than two months.)
I should massage my feet.
(Gosh, I should massage my feet.)
It's really hitting the spot.
Oh, my. This is amazing.
It's really good when you reduce leg swelling...
or when you relieve the heavy feeling in your legs.
Really?
I'm hungry.
Shall we go for a walk, Haetnim?
Joy, you're not the studious type either.
- Sorry? - You're not the studious type.
- Studious. - I got good grades, though.
I'm good at cramming for exams.
I used to cram for exams when I was in school.
Kian84 also said that he brought out the best performance...
right before the deadline.
I get what he means.
If I memorize the terms like putting them in my head...
right before the exam,
I can answer them well.
So I think I'm pretty good at cramming for exams.
You do get superhuman power.
(I get what you mean.)
So I'm not worried.
I know my future self will take care of it.
(She knows her stuff.)
Actually, I flipped open the problem-solving book in the taxi.
The magical problem-solving book?
(She bought the problem-solving book at the stationery store.)
(She thought of a worry in her head and opened the book.)
(Amazed)
This is the worry I had in my head.
"I'm so bad at this."
"Will I be able to get the certificate?"
And this came up.
"Even when you're at Level One, you defeat the boss in the end."
(Even when you're at Level 1, you defeat the boss in the end.)
I think it's right.
When we play games, we begin at Level One.
But if you keep working hard, you defeat the boss in the end.
But if you don't work hard,
- you finish at Level One. - That's right.
- I'll show you how I pass it. - You'll show us...
how you pass the written exam, right?
Yes!
Today was a difficult day at Level One.
But one day, I'll be able to get the pet groomer certificate,
the boss I'm aiming for.
I'll defeat it.
Haetnim, you're here.
(You can do it!)
(Level 1 Begins Now)
(Next story)
(Real runner Run84 is running again today.)
(Where did he go in the middle of running?)
(The Jeju house where Alkong and Dalkong welcome him)
(Last winter, )
(he met them through the adoption center.)
(Alkong and Dalkong became his family.)
(Barking)
(Be quiet.)
(Who are you?)
(Quiet!)
(The brothers are still awkward.)
(I'll take you to your daycare center.)
(Dalkong became the class president.)
(The class president?)
(A competent dog who beat 6-to-1 odds)
(They are 6 dogs, not 6 people.)
(There's a dog pledge. The pledge is even more annoying.)
(With the cutest campaign pledge, )
(his younger brother became the class president, )
(which Kian84 couldn't.)
(The mother's eyes are filled with love.)
(Dignified)
(Sullen)
(He feels the weight of the eldest son.)
(He may be confused, )
(but it's good as long as his mother is happy.)
(Eldest Son Kian84's Day)
(Sleeping soundly)
(Snoring)
(Struggling)
(What did your wife say?)
(I'm single.)
(The comedian whom everyone thought was married)
(Views: 1.83 million, Views: 1.59 million)
(Views: 1.22 million)
(He took over YouTube with his energy.)
(He definitely looks married.)
(He's been living alone for 19 years.)
(Comedian Lee Seon Min)
Okay.
(His fridge is full.)
(Cooking for myself is my happiness.)
(Scanning the fridge with hawk eyes to empty it)
(Putting it down)
(His technique of rinsing garlic)
(Anchovy broth he made himself)
(He made breakfast in no time.)
(This is the know-how of 19 years of living alone.)
(He skillfully emptied his fridge for a meal.)
(Hey, Min!)
(Facetiming with his sister)
(And his nephew and niece)
(Did you do well on the exams?)
(I got 96 points on average.)
(The uncle is proud.)
(It's the niece's birthday.)
(Ask him to get you a gift.)
(Uncle, buy me a gift.)
(Don't you miss Uncle?)
(Affectionate)
(Definitely a Man Who Lives Alone)